sup everyone k was one two three four
five four with a very special video
about some houses of adultery and offer
hey maybe I should borrow this in I
don't know trouble dog picks well I
didn't have to think too long cuz I
decided hell yeah I'm doing it I got
blue pink green and orange I couldn't
find y'all and Bobby's over but oh well
even if I did use yellow Bobby I
wouldn't show up anyways just to live so
just use orange points for that
okay everyone here we go boom oh
now first off and you can wonder what is
going to be guess I'll just starve a
Sonic and then yeah now they continue
off of a whole that looks that
looks good mmm
I'm not a shove it up my ass I
lost him II talked to big Mick Sox ma
he's a happy little badass make his eyes
up and walks he can be staring at saw at
Bobby's fine great boots that I like to
call his ass will have
he is so happy that he is going to
witness socks ass I bought his ass that
he just cannot believe his eyes oh my
God look at that everyone oh my God
oh yeah I got five there we go
haven't we give sock a cute little ass
oh my God nothing be good
don't forget shoes now and there we go
everyone oh there we go one's a Sonic
Sonic the Hedgehog next we're gonna be
getting on I guess you could call this
to the toil no I think about it
let me tweet I'm good well Barbie hot
this for how this to them
we're gonna go
I give obvious beautiful house he's big
luscious lips thank you next oh I try to
connect up next we're going to make
Bobby us also beautiful la golden lock
well well that what I've been blowing a
bit oh my God look at that it's like
blowing in the wind like that yeah oh my
God
no but make his eyes are cute like he
just caught Sun staring at his ass he's
like blushing a bit oh wait you pink for
the boss
he's like blushing I maybe because
Bobby's got a bathroom like taking a
and he didn't know the talk walking
the bathroom while I was that oh my God
he good oh hmm next we got to give
Bobby's he's big beautiful muscles cuz
we all know how buff he is oh my God
well I'll be flexing since wall sock
dudes walking he's taking taking this
time to act sexy for his oh my God
mmm come on oh my God that's good that's
good God I add all these
moths
hmm well Bobby shaking that ass
mmm well idle their lines right here to
show me like shaking that oh my
God mmm
look at that it's like going crazy up in
here now - you said since I can't show
on YouTube it is before adults and
she'll just have his leg be covering his
crotch so that it's it's child friendly
I out I want it's a well family friendly
so kid won't go tell her they can watch
my videos still use flexing mmm
there it is here you know what we're
done yeah I'm not gonna protect you this
I need sure good mix on flushing - mmm
oh my God mmm hmm mmm
he even bought with butters lush oh my
God
there you go of one and that is how you
draw a queue ask for dark picture mm-hmm
hope you do a